I saw it and guessed the name.
What was it?
We are going to the park.
Good morning.
I'm so excited that I rarely see you in
recent years.
We came to Kobayashi Farm in
Ishinomaki.
Kobayashi Farm!
I love it.
I'm going to the park.
You all like strawberries, right?
Yes!
It's the season, so we came to the
strawberry farm.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
But, we got a question from the adults.
When we went to see the strawberries,
they said they were all sold out.
The adults told us that.
So, we brought the two people who are
most suspicious.
I don't think so.
No, I don't think so.
The person who eats a lot of
strawberries is the criminal.
There are five kinds of strawberries in
front of us.
Wow!
There are five kinds.
From here,
Burimote
Sweet!
And, Kuchiotame
And, Queen Berry
Sweet!
And, Rage Berry
Premium!
And, Nico Nico Berry!
Yay!
You can eat all the strawberries on
this plate.
Yes!
You can eat all of them, but we will
give you a time limit.
30 minutes.
30 minutes?
The person who eats a lot in 30 minutes
is the culprit.
You are the culprit.
That's good.
Let's eat.
I will eat it.
You can eat all of them in 30 minutes.
When you eat, you will be silent.
Please say something.
Are you ready?
Let's eat.
Who will eat first?
I will eat it.
You are cute.
Who will eat first?
I will eat it.
Let's eat.
Please subscribe to my channel.
I won!
I'll have another one.
It's sweet.
But, it's refreshing.
It's like juice.
Next, I'll have Bu-chan-utama.
Isn't it great?
It's a great shape.
It's like a sample.
How is it?
They have different tastes.
What is it?
You can eat all of them, but I
recommend you to eat this one.
The tip of this is sweet.
It's like juice or sweets.
I understood it's juice.
Next.
I'm curious about this one.
It's grape.
It's green berry.
Let's eat.
It's a good size. It looks easy to eat.
What?
Wait, one more time.
Grape?
What?
A cat is coming.
Please subscribe to this channel.
It's so soothing.
What's with the strawberry and the cat?
It's the best.
It's so cute.
And this is...
You're back.
I'm back.
I know what it is.
I think if you close your eyes and eat
it...
How do you call it?
It's like a strawberry.
It's a strange feeling.
It's my first time.
But the taste is different.
Next.
Nikoniko Berry.
Let's eat.
I'm full.
I feel the chocolate at the end.
Really?
The sweetness at the end is like this.
This is like this.
Help me.
You don't like the food report?
This is a raisin.
I eat this.
It's soft.
It's soft and sweet.
I like this.
Which one do you like?
I've decided.
I'll say it with the count of three.
One, two, three!
That's not fair.
I like this one and this one.
Really?
So, the one with the most votes is the
winner.
I think I have a preference.
I like sweet strawberries, so I think I
like the one with the sweetest taste.
But if you eat more, it might change.
So, let's eat!
This one has a different taste.
And the shape is different.
I saw the name of the strawberry and it
was the same.
What's the name?
It's a strange name.
Do you eat strawberries with condensed
milk?
Do you drink it?
It's beautiful.
It's delicious.
It's not a plate of strawberries, but
800g.
So,
It's a lot.
So, there are five plates.
There are 4kg of strawberries in front
of you.
There are.
I can eat them all.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, isn't it?
They answered the questions 10 minutes
later than them.
Kobayashi Noen-san, if you contact us,
we can give you this.
There is no time limit.
But there are many people who can't eat
it.
You can take the rest home.
How kind!
If you don't finish it, you can eat it.
I will eat it.
It's not that luxurious.
When I was in elementary school, I went
on a school trip.
I ate 28 grapefruits of Vikings.
I was called grapefruit.
I am a black person.
Are you OK?
If you upload this video, you will be
called grapefruit.
But, if you are called strawberry, you
are cute.
I was called strawberry by my friend.
Do I look delicious?
You said, do I look delicious.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Delicious.
It's fun to eat and talk.
Petals.
I ate it.
Is it that light?
Uchi-Otome is gone.
I ate it.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It was popular at first, but it hasn't
changed.
But it changes the taste.
It's delicious when you eat it in the
middle.
I'm going to do my best.
Can I give you a place to walk?
I want to eat it.
I'll wait for you.
I'm waiting for you.
Thank you for watching.
I was sleeping.
It's raining.
I'm here.
Did you like it?
I was so happy.
It's a special berry.
It's gone.
Thank you for watching!
Let's do the gyu-tai.
OK.
Thank you for watching.
What?
No, no, no.
What's wrong?
Strawberries are here.
I can't sing.
Do you want to sing?
Yes, I do.
What song?
I'm away from strawberries.
You're far away from the camera, right?
That's good.
It's a moving video.
I'm eating deliciously.
I'm getting a lot of noise.
I'll turn off the air conditioner.
I'll turn on the air conditioner.
Thank you for watching.
It's good. It has a musical effect.
I liked the music the most.
I can change my personality.
Please sing a song that has your own
part.
I see.
I'm dancing to the music.
Thank you.
container
She said she walks lol
2nd variation
while walking
lol
Muraria...
I think everyone is surprised.
I think it was a premise that it
wouldn't disappear.
Can I look this way?
Yes.
OK.
Wait a minute.
Thank you for watching.
It's a good song, so I'm trying to get
it right.
That's right.
Yes, yes, thank you for your hard work.
It's amazing.
It's really a strawberry.
But it was delicious.
If it wasn't for this strawberry, it
wouldn't have been made.
There are so many flavors.
I don't care about it.
It's a level.
How many did you eat at a time?
This one?
Let's count.
OK.
Count the number of balls.
I got it.
Otherwise, Tachibana will definitely be
in the middle.
Because it's a secret.
That's terrible.
Let's count the number of balls.
OK.
One, two, three, four.
85, 86, 87.
Oh, my God.
89, 90.
Did you eat that much?
92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98.
That's right.
Kitami-san is...
Thank you for watching.
How old are you?
I'm about the same age as you.
I think you are 87 years old.
No, I'm 87.
I'm 108 years old.
So, there are 7 members who are not
here today.
The one who is eating the most is
Hachibana, as we expected.
I'm the culprit.
If you don't have a strawberry, please
look for Hachibana.
I got it.
But there may be other culprits.
Let's do it again someday if we can.
Next time, we will hunt strawberries.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please try to eat at Kobayashi Farm.
Please try to compare the taste.
See you next week. Bye-bye.